Finding Aid for the Stanley Kramer Papers LSC.0161
UCLA Library Special Collections
Stanley Kramer papers
1945-1984
UCLA Library Special Collections
LSC.0161
195.0 linear feet (316 boxes, 37 cartons, and 2 oversize boxes.)
9.5 linear feet (11 unprocessed boxes)
11 audiovisual carriers (4 audiocassettes, 7 videocassettes)
Stanley Kramer (1913- ) was born in New York City. He began working in the film industry in the 1930s as a researcher, film editor, and writer, eventually working his way up to the position of associate producer by the early 1940s. Following World War II, he formed an independent motion picture company and produced modest-budget films. In 1951, he brought his company as an autonomous unit under the banner of Columbia Pictures. After 1955, Kramer directed and produced films receiving numerous awards and Academy Award nominations. The collection contains production files for Kramer's films, stills, scripts, audio tapes, ephemera, related correspondence, and memorabilia.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: This collection contains both processed and unprocessed audiovisual materials. Audiovisual materials are not currently available for access, unless otherwise noted in a Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note at the series and file levels. All requests to access processed digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Stanley Kramer, 1969-1984.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID:9919730283606533
Biography
Kramer was born on September 23, 1913 in New York City; attended New York University; in the film industry since the mid-30s as a researcher, film editor, and writer, he worked his way up to the position of associate producer by the early 1940s; following World War II, he formed an independent motion picture company, Screen Plays Incorporated, and produced modest-budget films; in 1951, he brought his company as an autonomous unit under the banner of Columbia Pictures; in 1954 the arrangement was terminated by mutual consent; after 1955, Kramer directed and produced films, including: The Pride and the Passion (1957), On the Beach (1959), It's a Mad Mad Mad Mad World (1963); in 1961 he received the Irving G. Thalberg Award from the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences; six of Kramer's films as a director or producer earned Academy Award nominations: High Noon (1952), The Caine Mutiny (1954), The Defiant Ones (1958), Judgment at Nuremberg (1961), Ship of Fools (1965), and Guess Who's Coming to Dinner (1967); in 1991 he was honored with the Producers Guild's David O. Selznick Award.
Scope and Content
Collection contains production files for Kramer's films. Also includes stills, scripts, audio tapes, ephemera, related correspondence, and memorabilia.
Motion picture producers and directors -- Archives.; Kramer, Stanley--Archives.
- Films, (Document Boxes)
  - Andersonville (not produced). (Box 91)
    - Copies of first draft:, May 12, 1958.
    - Copies of first estimating draft by Abby Mann, February 14, 1966. (Box 92)
    - Production files (Breakdown sheets - Harper) (Box 93)
    - Production files (Honey - Reading file) (Box 94)
    - Production files (Scripts). (Box 95)
    - Production files (Sidney, George - Writers). (Box 96)
    - Research books and data:, 32 items. (Box 97, Box 98, Box 99, Box 100, Box 101, Box 102)
      General note
      See also: Boxes 325, 367.
    - Phonograph records, music of the Civil War. (Box 325)
    - Script, n.d.
      Missing-not received.
    - First estimating draft:, February 24, 1966. (Box 230)
    - Production manager's breakdown strips. (Box 367)
      Addition, June 20, 1975.
  - Bless the Beasts and Children:
    - Production Materials
      - Cast & Crew. (Box 132)
      - Program notes. (Box 132)
      - Production notes. (Box 132)
      - Releases. (Box 132)
      - Conservation Directory, 1971. (Box 132)
      - Telecompanion, July 1971. (Box 132)
      - Salt Lake City Television Shows, Tape transcripts. (Box 132)
      - Phoenix. (Box 132)
      - New York. (Box 133)
      - Dallas. (Box 133)
      - Chicago. (Box 133)
      - Boston (Box 133)
      - Book Reviews. (Box 133)
      - Awards. (Box 133)
      - Book Correspondence. (Box 133)
      - Correspondence (Miscellaneous). (Box 133)
      - Correspondence file (DAILY). (Box 133)
      - Censorship controversies. (Box 133)
      - Key Set Stills (Captions). (Box 133)
      - Combined Continuities (Box 133)
      - Actors--Stunt Players (Daily and Weekly Contracts). (Box 134)
      - Chapin, Miles (Shecker) -- Contract (Box 134)
      - Glaser, Darel [(Goodenow)--Contract]. (Box 134)
      - Ketchum, Dave [(Camp Director)--Contract]. (Box 134)
      - Kramer, Bob [(Lally I)--Contract]. (Box 134)
      - Leonard, Jack E. [(Sid Shecker)--Contract]. (Box 134)
      - Mumy, Bill [(Teft)--Contract]. (Box 134)
      - Robins, Barry [(Cotton)--Contract]. (Box 134)
      - Swofford, Ken [(Wheaties)--Contract]. (Box 134)
      - Vahanian, Marc [(Lally II)--Contract]. (Box 134)
      - American Humane Association, The. (Box 134)
      - Awards. (Box 134)
      - Beck, Myer Page (Sales Representative--agreement). (Box 134)
      - Benoff, Mac (writer)--Contract. (Box 134)
      - Grosses. (Box 133)
      - Billing. (Box 133)
      - Income from picture. (Box 138)
      - Budget (Cost Reports)--Pre-production & production cost. (Box 134)
      - Budget--Estimated Detail. (Box 134)
      - Call Sheet. (Box 134)
      - Cast & Crew Lists. (Box 134)
      - Columbia Pictures--Correspondence. (Box 134)
      - Comments, Congratulations, Quotes, etc. (file #1). (Box 134)
      - Comments, Congratulations, Quotes, etc. (file #3). (Box 135)
      - Continuities Combined (Cutting & Dialogue). (Box 135)
      - Claim - Another Mother for Peace (re-advertisement logo). (Box 135)
      - Credits--Main Title & Advertising. (Box 135)
      - Comments, Congratulations, Quotes, etc. (file #2). (Box 135)
      - Crank letters. (Box 135)
      - Daily Production Reports. (Box 135)
      - Day out of days schedule. (Box 135)
      - Doubleday (Publisher) Advertisements. (Box 135)
      - Doubleday (Publisher) Correspondence. (Box 135)
      - Ferguson, Robert (V. Pages advertisements, publicity & Expl.) Correspondence. (Box 135)
      - Film Festivals - Canada (Stratford - Ontario) San Francisco, Cannes. (Box 135)
      - Film Festival - Berlin. (Box 135)
      - Film Festival - Moscow. (Box 136)
      - Gordon, Billy - Casting Director. (Box 136)
      - Toronto. (Box 136)
      - Expenses. (Box 136)
      - Educational Contracts (Box 136)
      - Trade Clips. (Box 136)
      - Photography and photographers. (Box 136)
      - Photo captions. (Box 136)
      - Previews. (Box 136)
      - Playdates. (Box 136)
      - Music. (Box 136)
      - Locations. (Box 136)
      - Releases (Ed Fischer copy). (Box 137)
      - Previews--Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions. (Box 137)
      - Synopsis (short). (Box 137)
      - Synopsis (long). (Box 137)
      - Study Guides. (Box 137)
      - Hidden Valley Ranch (Prescott, Arizona - Dr. R.B. Nichols) Location Contract. (Box 137)
      - Hotel Lists. (Box 137)
      - If Poem by Rudyard Kipling. (Box 138)
      - Insurance. (Box 138)
      - Rothers, Incorporated (Denver, Colorado. re Bison herd). (Box 138)
      - Kramer, Stanley--Miscellaneous. (Box 138)
      - Kramer, Stanley. (Box 138)
      - Location Auditor--Harry Kohoyda--Correspondence). (Box 138)
      - Movement lists. (Box 138)
      - MPAA (Motion Picture Association of America) Title registration & code no. (Box 138)
      - Music - album. (Box 138)
      - Music - A&M Records. (Box 138)
      - Music - Barry DeVorzon and Perry Botkin, Jr.--Contract (Box 138)
        Scope and Contents note
        (songwriter)
        (composer)
      - Music - Carpenters - Song, Bless the Beasts and Children Agreement. (Box 138)
      - Music - Music Breakdown. (Box 138)
      - Music Cue Sheet. (Box 138)
      - Music - Song, It's a Beautiful Day by Bill Mumy/Paul H. Gordon. (Box 138)
      - Music - Song, Bless the Beasts and the Children. (Box 138)
      - Music--Miscellaneous Correspondence. (Box 138)
      - Music - Spotting Notes. (Box 139)
      - Film Festival - Moscow. (Box 138)
      - National Rifle Assocaition; Firearms Association. (Box 138)
      - Poems on Dining Room Wall; Hidden Valley Ranch A State of Mind. (Box 138)
      - Production Notes. (Box 138)
      - Programs. (Box 138)
      - Reviews--Book. (Box 139)
      - Reviews--Trades - Magazines, Newspapers. (Box 139)
      - Reviews. (Box 140)
      - Screenings. (Box 139)
      - Shipments, Mailings. (Box 139)
      - Shooting Schedule. (Box 139)
      - Simon & Schuster, Incorporated--Publisher Novelization of Screen. Paperback). (Box 139)
      - Swarthout, Glendon (author)--agreement. (Box 139)
      - Swarthout, Glendon (author)--Correspondence. (Box 139)
      - Television Spot Censorship Story (Box 139)
      - Theatre openings. (Box 139)
      - Editorial. (Box 139)
      - Ivan Volkman--Production Manager--Correspondence. (Box 139)
      - Weiss, Voisin, Cannon, Incorporated (Stockbrokers) - Beverly Hills - Location. (Box 139)
      - Zagon, Schiff, Hirsch, Levine, & Mark--Correspondence. (Box 139)
    - Publicity
      - Press Releases. (Box 139)
      - Press, Radio, College Lists from A&M Records. (Box 132)
      - Preview Screening, New York Alice Tulley Hall, June 21, 1971. (Box 138)
      - Requests for Premiere, Special Screenings, etc. (Box 139)
      - Glass, George--Correspondence. (Box 139)
      - appearances: TV/Radio, Personal & Telephone Interviews. (Box 138)
      - Advertisements. (Box 138)
      - Beck, Myer P.--Correspondence. (Box 138)
      - Columbia Pictures--Correspondence. (Box 139)
      - M. Kay (Booker)--Correspondence. (Box 139)
      - Advertisements. (Box 132)
      - Trailer (TV clips). (Box 139)
      - Television Spot 1 minute (Stan Freberg). (Box 139)
      - Press Kit. (Box 139)
      - Magazine clips. (Box 136)
      - Promotion (Ecology Organizations). (Box 137)
      - Trailers. (Box 137)
      - Promotion (New York screening). (Box 137)
      - Promotion (Miscellaneous). (Box 137)
      - Radio/TV Promotion. (Box 137)
    - Scripts
      - 1. First draft:; revised, May 22, 1970 June 12, 1970. (Box 140)
      - 2. Revised first draft:, June 12, 1970. (Box 140)
      - 3. Final draft: (as shot). Revised, June 18, 1970 July 29, 1970. (Box 140)
      - 4. Final draft: (as shot). Revised, June 18, 1970 July 29, 1970. (Box 140)
      - 5. Final draft: (as shot). Revised, June 18, 1970 July 29, 1970. (Box 140)
      - 6. Final draft: (as shot). Revised, June 18, 1970 July 29, 1970. (Box 140)
      - 6a. Final draft: (as shot)., June 18, 1970 (Box 140)
      - 7. Final draft: (as shot)., June 18, 1970 (Box 141)
      - 8. Final draft: (as shot)., June 18, 1970 (Box 141)
      - 9. S. Kramer Personal Final draft: (Revised, June 18, 1970. September 10, 1970. (Box 141)
      - 10. S. Kramer Personal Shooting Script. Page breakdown by scenes. Flashbacks in chronological order. (Box 141)
        NOTE: See Folders, 46. Continuities Combined (Cutting & Dialogue).
      - 6. Miscellaneous pages of revisions, (approximately 100) (Box 144)
    - Stills
      - Production Stills (Proof Sheets), approximately 200. (Box 141)
      - Proofs 8×10 taken in New York. (Box 144)
    - Tapes
      - 1. Preview #1. (Box 141)
      - 2. Preview #2. (Box 141)
      - 3. Stan Freberg Radio Spot #1. (Box 142)
      - 4. Stan Freberg Radio Spot #1. (Box 142)
      - 5. Stan Freberg Radio Spot #1. (Box 142)
      - 6. Stan Freberg Radio Spot #1. (Box 142)
      - 7. Stan Freberg Radio Spot #1. (Box 142)
      - 8. Preview #1, June 1971. (Box 142)
      - 9. Preview #2, June 1971. (Box 142)
      - 10. 11th Hour interview. (Box 143)
      - 11. Interview with M. Jackson, April 9, 1972. (Box 143)
      - 12. KABC Presentation, October 21, 1960. (Box 143)
      - 13. Face to Face. (Box 143)
    - Miscellany
      - Bless the Beasts and Children (1 vol.) - the story as it follows in the book without the flashbacks (Mac Benoff). (Box 143)
      - Bless the Beasts & the Children - combined continuities. (Folder 5)
      - Bless the Beasts and Children (17 discs) - song recorded by The Carpenters: Bless the Beasts and the Children. (Box 143)
      - Bless the Beasts and the Children. (Box 361)
        Proofs (nos. 1-4534) and stills (2).
      - Swarthout,Glendon. Bless the Beasts and Children., (4 copies) (Box 144)
      - Editorials (Censorship). (Box 144)
      - Student evaluations., 65 items. (Box 144)
      - Audience reaction cards, (approximately 1200) (Box 145)
  - The Caine Mutiny, 1954.
    - Final shooting script, heavily annotated by Edward Dmytryk. (Box 7)
    - Academy Award nomination plaque for best picture, 1954. (Box 301)
    - Model ship. (Box 301)
    - 30 stills, 10 × 13,on heavy board, bound together. (Box 301)
    - 16 × 20 framed still photograph, autographed by the cast.
    - Folder of awards. (Box 7)
    - 400 production stills, 8 × 10. (Box 8)
      See also: Boxes 301, 357.
    - Script. Final draft: Screenplay by Stanley Roberts., May 6, 1953. (Box 294)
  - The Champion, (1949).
    - Final shooting script, annotated by Mark Robson. (Box 1)
    - 24 Storyboards. (Box 372, Folder 5)
    - 27 Set Stills (Box 372, Folder 4)
    - Statuette of prize fighter with one hand (Kirk Douglas). (Box 301)
    - 1 Shooting Schedule (Box 372, Folder 6)
    - Photo Play Magazine Award. (Box 1)
      See also: Boxes 301, 336.
    - 16 × 20 framed still photograph (Kirk Douglas).
      missing December 1985
    - Script. Screenplay by Carl Foreman., ca. 1948. (Box 294)
    - Scrapbook: The Champion and Home of the Brave. (Box 336)
  - A Child is Waiting, 1963.
    - Final draft screenplay, January 3, 1962. (Box 54)
    - Final draft: (4)., January 3, 1962 (Box 240)
    - Final draft: (3)., January 3, 1962 (Box 230)
    - Dialogue and cutting continuity scripts. (Box 54)
    - Dialogue continuity. (Box 240)
    - Cutting continuity. (Box 240)
    - Press clippings. (Box 345)
    - Music for A Child Is Waiting. (Box 110)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Tape recording
    - Music sketches and lead sheets. (Box 345, Box 346, Box 347)
    - Johannesburg Film Society plaque. (Box 356)
    - California Senate plaque, 1963. (Box 356)
    - Folder of awards. (Box 54)
    - Production files (Actors' Contracts - Cast and crew lists). (Box 54)
    - Production files (Daily production reports - M.P.P.A.). (Box 55)
    - Production files (Music). (Box 56)
    - Production files (Publicity - Wardrobe). (Box 57)
    - 360 production stills. (Box 58)
    - 360 production stills. (Box 59)
      See also: Boxes 345, 346, 347, 356.
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. Releases. (Box 126)
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. Reviews (Box 126)
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. Feature stories. (Box 126)
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. Tear Sheets. (Box 126)
  - Cyrano de Bergerac, 1950.
    - Final shooting script, heavily annotated by Carl Foreman. (Box 3)
    - Folder of newsclippings. (Box 3)
    - Folder of awards. (Box 3)
    - 184 stills, 8 × 10. (Box 3)
    - Poster of Cyrano de Bergerac. Japan, 1950.; 52 × 73 cm. (Box 327)
      See also: Box 3, and index.
    - Poster of Cyrano de Bergerac, Japan, One sheet., 1950. (Box 327)
    - Cleveland Film Critics Trophy for Cyrano de Bergerac, 1951. (Box 330)
    - Christian Herald plaque for Cyrano de Bergerac,, Home of the Brave,, The Men, 1951 1949 1950.; Three items. (Box 120)
    - 16 × 20 framed still photograph (Jose Ferrer)
    - Press Book (Box 131)
    - 24 Storyboards. (Box 373, Folder 2)
    - 30 Storyboards. (Box 373, Folder 1)
    - 30 Storyboards. (Box 372, Folder 13)
    - 28 Storyboards. (Box 372, Folder 11)
    - 29 Storyboards. (Box 372, Folder 10)
    - 29 Storyboards. (Box 372, Folder 12)
    - Cup from Jose Ferrer (Cyrano de Bergerac). (Box 328)
    - Exhibitor Laurel Award plaque for Dramatic Presentation,, Top Ten Producer-Director,, Cyrano de Bergerac,, High Noon, 1959 1963-1964 1950-1951 1952-1953.; Five items. (Box 122)
    - Black Tights--Correspondence. (Box 146)
    - Story Development Fund.
      See Box 294.
    - Final Verdict Sale, December 22, 1967.
    - NTA - 4 Star Television Rights - High Noon. (Box 146)
    - Cyrano - Never judge a man by his nose. (Box 146)
    - Cyrano - Saperstein--Magoo Cartoons) - Television Correspondence. (Box 146)
    - Cyrano--Van Loewen & O'Brien)--Correspondence. (Box 146)
    - White, Onna (Choreographer--Contract).
    - Geller, Mike (Plagiarism). (Box 147)
    - Segal, Erich (writer) Correspondence.
    - Segal, Erich (writer) Contract.
    - Publicity - Press Releases.
    - MPAA (Motion Picture Association of America).
    - Music - Artists (Performers, Composers & Agents).
    - Music--Miscellaneous correspondence.
    - Legrand, Michel (composer & conductor) Contract. (Box 147)
    - Mercer, Johnny (songwriter) Contract. (Box 147)
    - NBC-TV. Proposed musical Cyrano (Richard Graham). (Box 147)
    - Harburg, E.Y. & Burton Lane. (Box 147)
    - Job Applications. (Box 147)
    - Script. Cyrano de Bergerac by Edmond Rostand. Second draft screenplay by Carl Foreman. (Box 147)
    - Script. Screenplay by Carl Foreman. From the play by Edmond Rostand. (Box 147)
    - Cutting and dialogue continuity. (Box 147)
    - Actors & Agents. (Box 147)
    - Agents - Technical Employment. (Box 147)
    - Releases. (Box 147)
    - Costumes--Correspondence. (Box 147)
    - Comments, Congrats, quotes, etc. (Box 147)
    - Columbia Pictures Corporation - Purchase Agreement. (Box 147)
    - Clips--Newspapers. (Box 147)
    - Clips--Trades. (Box 147)
    - Budget--Cost Reports. (Box 147)
    - Bart, Lionel--Correspondence. (Box 147)
    - Crank letters. (Box 147)
    - Conflicts--Miscellaneous (Box 147)
    - Davis, Jr., Sammy--Contract. (Box 147)
    - Cyrano (Short). Sent to Film Archive, UCLA, Theatre Arts Department.
    - Cyrano Corporation--Correspondence & Financial Statements, Minutes. (Box 146)
    - Cyrano Corporation--High Noon Anthology - Five Classic Screenplays. (Box 146)
    - Cyrano Corporation--David Merrick's Musical Play - Cyrano de Bergerac--Correspondence and agreement. (Box 146)
  - Death of a Salesman, 1951.
    - Final shooting script, including all changes, cast lists, and production breakdown. (Box 4)
    - Production material (Box 294)
    - Modern Photography plaque, 1952. (Box 339)
    - Folder of newsclippings. (Box 4)
    - Folder of awards. (Box 4)
      See also: Box 339.
    - 30 Storyboards. (Box 373, Folder 11)
    - 30 Storyboards. (Box 373, Folder 12)
    - 21 Storyboards. (Box 373, Folder 13)
    - Script. Final draft: Screenplay by Stanley Roberts., August 3, 1951.
    - American Weekly plaque for Death of A Salesman, 1952. (Box 330)
  - The Defiant Ones, 1958.
    - 106 production stills, 8 × 10. (Box 17)
    - 16 phonograph record, music. (Box 357)
    - British Film Academy plaque for best film. (Box 357)
    - 16 × 20 framed still photograph (Sidney Poitier).
      missing December 1989.
    - Script., n.d. (Box 241)
    - Script., January 20, 1950. (Box 241)
    - Script., January 28, 1958. (Box 241)
    - Script, January 28, 1958. (Box 240)
    - Cutting and dialogue. (Box 241)
    - Cutting continuity (3). (Box 241)
    - Original first draft screenplay. (Box 17)
    - Final draft screenplay, heavily annotated by Stanley Kramer, with scene breakdown on each page. (Box 17)
    - Photograph of Stanley Kramer, 11 × 14. (Box 17)
    - Editors' Trophy, 1958. (Box 366)
    - Hollywood Foreign Press statue for Best Picture. (Box 304)
    - Folder of awards. (Box 17)
    - New York Film Critics plaque for Best Picture, 1958. (Box 304)
    - New York Film Critics plaque for Best Director, 1958. (Box 304)
    - Page One Award plaque,, in case., June 26, 1959 (Box 304)
    - Sterling silver leg irons (Stanley Kramer, 1958). (Box 304)
    - Academy Award plaque for nomination for Best Picture, 1958. (Box 304)
    - Academy Award plaque for nomination for Best Director. (Box 304)
    - Berlin Film Festival scrapbook containing stills and publicity. (Box 337)
    - Screen Directors' Guild plaque for nomination for Best Director. (Box 304)
    - Screen Producers' Guild certificate for nomination for Best Producer, framed. (Box 304)
    - John Anson Ford Plaque for The Defiant Ones, 1958. (Box 331)
    - Valladolid, Spain, plaque for The Defiant Ones, April 1959. (Box 123)
    - Los Angeles Urban League plaque for The Defiant Ones, 1958. (Box 123)
    - Production files. (Box 18)
    - 2-12 phono recordings, Long Gone. (Box 304)
    - Holograph lead sheets for music, 28 leaves. (Box 19)
      See also: Boxes 304, 337, 357, 366.
    - M. Beck Publicity and Correspondence. Negatives (Box 131)
      50 negatives.
    - Prof. Irwin R. Blacker. (Box 241)
    - Press Book (Box 131)
    - 50 stills and slides or transparencies. (Box 385)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 381, Folder 8)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 381, Folder 7)
    - 12 Storyboards. (Box 381, Folder 6)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 381, Folder 5)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 381, Folder 4)
    - 35 Storyboards. (Box 381, Folder 3)
  - Domino Killings (original title: The Domino Principle)
    - Production Materials
      - 1. Albert, Edward Jr. (Pine)--Contract, etc. (Box 148)
      - 2. Bergen, Candice (Doris)--Contract, etc. (Box 148)
      - 3. Rooney, Mickey (Spinenta)--Contract, etc. (Box 148)
      - 7. Hackman, Gene--Tucker)--Contract, etc. (Box 148)
      - 61. Actors--Day Player Contracts. (Box 151)
      - 4. Widmark, Richard (Tagge). (Box 148)
      - 5. Avco Embassy. (Box 148)
      - 6. The Domino Principle - Art Department. (Box 148)
      - 8. Wallach, Eli (Gen. Reser). (Box 148)
      - 9. Call Sheets., 2 Folders. (Box 148)
      - 10. Actors & Agents. (Box 148)
      - 11. Publicity on Prison (envelope/ads). (Box 148)
      - 12. Revised scenes from Domino, pp. 9, 15, 57., (approximately 30 copies) (Box 148)
      - 13. Location notes. (Box 148)
      - 14. Theatre Openings. (Box 148)
      - 15. Script Revisions--First Revised (Notations)., January 15 (Box 148)
      - 16. Gavin. (Box 149)
      - 17. William S. Gilmore. (Box 149)
      - 18. Editorial - Television version. (Box 149)
      - 19. Daily Production Reports. (Box 149)
      - 20. Credits--Main Title and Advertising. (Box 149)
      - 21. Crew. (Box 149)
      - 37. Cast & Crew Lists. (Box 150)
      - 22. Kappoff Music Services (Nathan Kappoff). (Box 149)
      - 23. Marstar. (Box 149)
      - 24. Location - San Francisco. (Box 149)
      - 25. Independent Casting. (Box 149)
      - 26. Insurance. (Box 149)
      - 27. Location - Puerta Vallarta. (Box 149)
      - 28. Kennedy, Adam--Contract, etc. (Box 149)
      - 29. Schedules. (Box 149)
      - 30. Script Distribution. (Box 149)
      - 31. Publicity, Press Correspondence. (Box 150)
      - 32. Publicity, Advertisements. (Box 150)
      - 46. Publicity, Strauss, John (CPR) Correspondence. (Box 150)
      - 53. Publicity Releases. (Box 150)
      - 33. Publicity, Beck, Meyer P., Correspondence. (Box 150)
      - 34. General. (Box 150)
      - 35. Location, San Quentin. (Box 150)
      - 36. Comments, Congratulations, Quotes, etc. (Box 150)
      - 38. Continuities Combined. (Box 150)
      - 39. Hotel lists. (Box 150)
      - 41. Brown - Kraft. (Box 150)
      - 40. Box Office Receipts. (Box 150)
      - 42. Business Expenses - S. Kramer. (Box 150)